For this hackathon, I'm really excited
to announce the release of cards402.com.
cards402.com is a full dashboard for
managing agent spend and beyond that, it
allows you to issue visas or
technically, the agent can issue
themselves a visa from their own wallet
balance. There's full spend limits,
there's full control, there's so much to
this. Let's get into a demo and I'll
just run you through it. Okay, so let's
just run through a quick demo of
cards402. So, firstly, I'm just going to
go to my dashboard and just do ash plus
test transistor.com. There's a full uh
transactional email service. Uh hop into
this. So, this is actually going to
email me a real code. Feel free to test
that yourself. Um
if you actually want to deploy this
yourself, you'll need to enter in quite
a lot of environment variables and
things, but you'll feel free. It's all
open source.
Um okay, so you can see here, this is
the immediate dashboard. Once we log in,
we can get some view of our agents and
our orders and what we've been up to. Um
approvals, so that's if a agent wants to
request approval from their human
operator for spend larger than their
limits. Uh analytics, merchants. Right
now, there's just the Visa uh card on
there, which you can see the limits on.
Uh the range is actually wrong there.
It's uh the minimum order is currently 2
cents. I've set it low so we can test
it, but eventually, when it's
production, I'll probably increase it a
little bit. Uh webhooks, you can have
alerts happening and things to your um
your own like Discord notifications or
whatever.
Uh there's a lot of different settings
here. I kept on adding features. So, uh
yeah, there's full UX, different UX. Um
there's a lot of bits. Um
all right, and you can obviously search
for transactions, too. So, let's get to
the meat of this all. Uh we're going to
set up an agent. So, I'm just going to
click a new agent here. I'm just going
to call it
test agent 22.
Create agent.
Uh this is the important thing. This is
the one-line setup. So, uh let's just
open a new
tab here and just do cloud. Uh so, you
can see we're starting from scratch and
I'm going to give it this one line here.
Now, if all goes to plan, it will deploy
its own open wallet standard, um,
the fork that Stef made at Stellar at
Development Foundation. It will create
its own, um, OWS wallet with Stellar and
Soroban support, um, and it will create
that link and claim. So, if we actually
click here, you can see the tracking.
Uh, this does take a little while.
There's quite a bit of a process of
setting up, um,
just because the agent has to kind of
understand what it's doing. Uh, so I'm
just going to accelerate this, um, fast
forward this bit.
Okay, you can see that was pretty quick.
Uh, just under a minute, we've got a
wallet address there. So, uh, now I'm
going to just send that wallet some, uh,
XLM. This is mainnet production.
Uh, so I'll just send it five XLM to
this wallet.
Uh, continue.
Review send.
And send. Um, so that's sending five XLM
to the agent's, um, open wallet
standard. Uh, wallet it is a fork of a
wallet standard, uh, not the actual real
one. I actually had to even fork Stef's
fork, um, with her thing to deploy it.
Okay, and then you can see that it's
recognized that there's funding on
there. So, now we can just ask it
purchase a 0.02
Visa card. Uh, Visa card. And let's let
it do that.
Um, obviously
Visa card details and things are
sensitive, but these are kind of like
one-time use cards. So, typically you
would make a purchase to actually then
immediately spend. If I press control O,
you'll see, uh,
the details, hopefully.
Uh, so this is it just reading like
skills.md, but here we should see
our details. We'll see like this needs
some improvement on the responsive UI.
Uh, but if we go to our agents here, you
can see, uh, orders, we can see it was
ordered there.
Um.
If we go to our agents, we can see uh
the balance there that it's deducted and
that's made that purchase. Um and then
the card's delivered. Uh so
obviously these are confidential um bits
of information. But there you go,
there's a quick overview. Feel free to
test out yourselves. Let me know if you
get any have any questions. Thank you
for watching.
Oh, yeah. I probably should have
mentioned that um
with the agents are like fully
configurable on their daily spending
limits, and monthly per order limits,
and then there's the approval. Um
I mean, this is for X402. It's not just
for Visa.
So, uh you could use this without using
the Visa side at all and just use this
as a spend management. Uh initially, I
started this with the idea of it being
focused on the Visa, so that's why it's
called Cards402. But realistically, I
see it as called a sort of a full agent
financial dashboard. So, I'll probably
rename it into you something else
because, you know, if you're running
fleets of agents or with spend controls
both in blockchain currency and fiat
currency and things, it goes far beyond
just a card delivery platform. Um I'm
sure you'll have fun looking around. Um
there are some planned features. Uh you
might see one there, the auto top-up. Uh
but yeah, there's quite a lot um here
already. So, please have a little look,
see what you think, um
and yeah, uh so
let me know if you have any questions.
Thank you for watching.